ONYEDIKACHI UDEH

GGSS Funtua, Katsina Nigeria +2348182179927 udehonyedikachi01@gmail.com Portfolio

Software developer and Machine Learning enthusiast passionate about technology and constant learning, with experience in developing web and mobile applications. Proficient with object-oriented programming languages as well as algorithms and data structures.

SKILLS

- **Programming Languages**: Python, PHP, Javascript.
- **DBMS**: MySQL, MongoDB.
- Frameworks: Express(Nodejs), React, React Native, Flask, Django, Laravel, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS.
- **Environment**: Linux/Unix, Windows.
- Others: Machine Learning, Web Scraping.

EXPERIENCE

Zurichat - Backend Developer

August 2021 - October 2021

• Developed some core functionalities powering the 'Company Sales Prospects' plugin in zuri.chat (An open-source, very flexible group communication tool).

ForeTrust Digital Consulting Ltd, Enugu, Nigeria - Trainee Developer

August 2018 - October 2020

- Developed a 'Computer Based Test' software for writing JAMB mock exams.
- Worked with ForeTrust developers to develop a web-based 'Training Management System' for the company.

EDUCATION

Godfrey Okoye University, Enugu, Nigeria - Bsc Computer Science

October 2017 - July 2021

St Patrick College Emene, Enugu, Nigeria - SSSC

September 2012 - July 2017

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Languages: English (Full), Igbo (Native), German (Elementary)

Hobbies: Cycling, Writing.